250 million, that's how much my business
has made in total last year.
But before that, here's every single business
I tried before winning.
Number one, the free training project.
So I actually started a non-profit
where I would just give away fitness services
in exchange for people donating money to a charity.
From there, I shifted that into a for-profit thing
for only my 20 best friends called Skinny the Swole
from the guys I was in the fraternity with.
From there, I didn't wanna keep doing that
because I wanted to be legit,
so I started a brick and mortar gym
called Transformation Center
that eventually became United Fitness.
That was brick and mortar.
I scaled that to six locations.
While I was going on with that,
I thought maybe I should start also a chiropractor agency
because I was pretty good at marketing and sales.
And then I thought, you know what,
why have two businesses when you could have three?
And I started a dental marketing agency.
And then I thought, hey, why have three businesses
when you could have four?
So then I started a gym turnaround business
where I would fly around from gym
and I would actually do gym launches
where I'd fill the gym up in 30 days,
then started scaling that out.
Obviously, Layla, smarter than me, was like,
hey, what if we did the one thing
that actually makes us money, which is launching gyms?
So I shut down the other two businesses,
even though I had different partners in all of them,
and even though I was the CEO slash Rainmaker in all of them,
I shut all of those down and went all in on gym launch.
I kept doing that, but then all of a sudden
that stopped working as well.
And so then we had the brilliant idea,
hey, Layla, you lost 100 pounds.
Why don't we start Queen Transformation?
We'll just sell directly to people online,
the way I had actually started this business
four or five years earlier, and we started doing that.
And so within a few days of absolute caffeine
and stimulant up to my eyeballs,
I wrote the best sales letter of my life,
started ring ads to it, and we started making money.
We scaled that for five years.
And then in that process,
we also started our supplement company, Prestige Labs,
the third year in the business.
And the fourth year, we started Allen,
which is a lead working software.
We sold all three of those companies in 2021, $46.2 million.
From there, we started acquisition.com
with the 40 plus million in distributions
and the $46 million sale.
We took the cash and started investing in companies.
And today, five years later,
our aggregate portfolio is $250 million a year.
The business that you're in right now
is probably not the one you're gonna end up in,
but the lessons you learn are the ones that you'll keep.